Register to The Benny Goodman Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Band and Combo Arrangements
  - JINGLE, JANGLE, JINGLE Kirkpatrick, Don, 1942 (Box 15C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: C312/86A
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt3/PGBD
  - JUBILEE (Box 15C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A287/220
  - JUBILEE Williams, George, 1958 (Box 15C, Folder 30)
  - JUBILESTA, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 15C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A288/40
  - JUMPIN' JIVE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 15C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A22/464
  - JUST A GIGOLO Harding, Buster, 1958 (Box 15D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B375
  - JUST AN IDEA Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 15D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: 119
    Parts: cl/saxT/PGBD
  - JUST GIVE ME TIME Boland, Francis, 1958 (Box 15D, Folder 35)
    Key: B flat minor
    Piano and guitar part are combined. Complete.
  - JUST LIKE TAKING CANDY FROM A BABY Henderson, Fletcher, 1940 (Box 15D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A61
  - JUST ONE OF THOSE THINGS (Box 15D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B116
  - JUST ONE OF THOSE THINGS Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 15D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: B116/37A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn2/PD
  - JUST ONE SMALL MOMENT Thompson, Sir Charles, 1939 (Box 15D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: A158
  - JUST PLAIN TALKIN' Dameron, Tadd, 5/1962 (Box 15E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: G32/306
  - JUST YOU AND I Woode, Henri, 1938 (Box 15E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: A159/463
  - JUST YOU JUST ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1945 (Box 15E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: A129/77/54/37
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB(2)/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - KATUSHA Prince, Bob, 3-4/1962 (Box 15E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: F21
    Vocal arrangement for Joya Sherrill. Complete.
  - KATUSHA Lipman, Joe, 1962 (Box 15E, Folder 44)
  - KEEP JUMPIN' (Box 15E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: D16
    Parts: saxAA/tpt2-3/B
    Tpt3 marked for "Cootie".
  - KEEP SMILING AT TROUBLE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B76/104/651/33
  - KEEPIN' OUT OF MISCHIEF NOW Murphy, Spud, 3/15/1935 (Box 16, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B74
  - KIM'S TUNE Rood, Hale, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A95/216
  - KINDA BLUESY Bunch, John, 1/1963 (Box 16, Folder 04)
    BG No.: F16/14
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/PB
    On reverse side of bass part there is music for "Lazy Afternoon" and "San Francisco".
  - KING PORTER Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - KING PORTER STOMP Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 05)
    BG No.: C245/24
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PBD
    Parts included from 1935 copy are: saxB/tpt1-4/BD. Others are from a later recopy. Horn can substitute for tbn3.
  - KING PORTER STOMP (Box 16, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A193
    Score: for added parts only
  - KING PORTER STOMP Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 07)
    BG No.: 10/K1/15
    Includes photocopies of: el/saxAATTB/tptl-3/tbnl-3/BD.; These parts are from a later recopy.
  - KING PORTER STOMP Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 7A)
    BG No.: 15
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2
    Recopy. Rhythm parts to complete this set, as played in the 1980's, are found in preceding arrangements labeled 15.
  - KNOCK ME A KISS Kirkpatrick, Don, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C326/44A
  - KOOL Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 16A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: 138
  - KYRIE Ogerman, Claus (Box 16A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: G7/K2
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PG(2)BD
  - LADY BE GOOD Henderson, Fletcher (Box 16A, Folder 10A)
    BG No.: 20
  - LADY IS A TRAMP, THE Phillips, Herb, 3/1961 (Box 16A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: C248/415
  - LADY WHO COULDN'T BE KISSED, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 16A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: B252/75
  - LADY WHO DIDN'T BELIEVE IN LOVE, THE Kirkpatrick, Don, 1942 (Box 16A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: B253
  - LADY WHO DIDN'T BELIEVE IN LOVE, THE (Box 16A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: C377/85A
  - LAMP IS LOW, THE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 16A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: C226/T4/122
    Score: sax (AATT) and guitar parts only
    Parts: cl/saxAATT(2)B/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Score transcribed by Bill Hood 6/9/1964. Score indicates that saxT2 is "reconstructed". Complete.
  - LAMP OF MEMORY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 16A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: B77
  - LET THERE BE LOVE Lipman, Joe, 5/2/1962 (Box 16A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: D438/26 9
  - LET'S DANCE (Box 16B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: A278
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PGBD
    Photocopies included for: cl/saxAATT/tpt3-4/tbn1-4/PGBD.
    There are no originals for: saxAlT2/GD.
  - LET'S DANCE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 16B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: A278/L5
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4(2)/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Original tpt4 and tbn3 are incomplete. (There is a full recopied tpt4.) Photocopies also of: el/saxTl/PB.
  - LET'S DANCE McEachern, Murray, 1960 (Box 16B, Folder 20)
    Parts: saxAT/tpt/rhythm lead sheet,V
    Key: E flat Includes part labeled " Jerry". This arrangement intended as "short opener".
  - LET'S DANCE (Box 16B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A278/0
    This arrangement is first 40 measures of BG no.A278/L5: intended as an opener.
  - LET'S DANCE Bassman, Sammy (Box 16B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A403/1
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - LET'S DANCE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 16B, Folder 23)
    Parts from a later recopy. Complete.
  - LET'S DANCE Stegmeyer, Bill, c.1960 (Box 16B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: D346/1A
  - LET'S DANCE, 1959 (Box 16B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: D346/1
    Parts: cl/saxAT/tpt/tbn/PGBV
  - LET'S DANCE Newsom, Tommy, 1/1963 (Box 16B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D346
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/PBD
  - LET'S DANCE Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 01)
  - LET'S DANCE (Box 16B, Folder 26A)
    BG No.: 1
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Piano part sketch only. Cl part used with this set in the 1980's can be found with "Swing Into Spring", 1959 arrangement.
  - LET'S DO IT Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 16C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B161
  - LET'S FACE THE MUSIC AND DANCE Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 16C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: A307
  - LET'S GET A WAY FROM IT ALL (TAG) Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - LET'S GET TOGETHER Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 16C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: 94
    Parts: cl/tpt2/GD
  - LET'S GIVE LOVE A CHANCE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 16C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: B162
  - LET'S GO HOME Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 16C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B163
  - LET'S SAY A PRAYER, 1942 (Box 16C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: C134/39A
  - LIFE GOES TO A PARTY James, Harry, 1937 (Box 16C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: A350/138
  - LIKE A BOLT FROM THE BLUE Noble, Jiggs, 1934 (Box 16C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: A153/217
  - LIKE YOUNG Davis, Buster (Box 34, Folder 05)
  - LILLETE (Box 16C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A190
  - LIMEHOUSE BLUES Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 16C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: 120
    Parts: saxT/BDV
    Original based on "Limehouse Blues".
  - LIMEHOUSE BLUES Murphy, Spud, 5/8/1935 (Box 16C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A400/28
  - LITTLE BIT INDEPENDENT Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 16C, Folder 38)
    BG No.: A216/34
  - LITTLE COQUETTE (Box 16C, Folder 38A)
    BG No.: C130/31
  - LITTLE FOOL Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 16C, Folder 39)
    BG No.: B164
  - LITTLE MAN WHO WASN'T THERE, THE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 16C, Folder 40)
    BG No.: A52
  - LIZA, 1/1963 (Box 16C, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B59/1
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/B
  - LIZA (Box 16D, Folder 42)
  - LOCH LOMOND Thornhill, Claude, 1937 (Box 16D, Folder 43)
    BG No.: D417/91
    Arrangement adapted by Jimmy Mundy.
  - LOCH LOMOND Thornhill, Claude, 1937 (Box 16D, Folder 44)
    Score: original and for added brass and saxB by Sid Feller
    Includes parts for original 5 brass (tpt2-3/tbn1-2). This arrangement adapted by Jimmy Mundy. Complete.
  - LONELY GOATHERD (#1) Karlin, Fred, 10-11/1959 (Box 16D, Folder 45)
    BG No.: D224
    SaxA doubles flute. Complete.
  - LONELY GOATHERD (#2) Karlin, Fred, 10-11/1959 (Box 16D, Folder 46)
    Includes 2 sheets labeled "Goatherd revision". Complete.
  - LONELY MOMENTS Williams, Mary Lou, 1947 (Box 16D, Folder 47)
    BG No.: 137
  - LONESOME ROAD Jenkins, Gordon, 5/1976 (Box 16E, Folder 48)
    BG No.: G142
    These parts are photocopies: el/saxA2T2B/tpt2-4/tbn2-4/GB.
    All sax parts double flute or clarinet. Complete.
  - LONESOME ROAD Rood, Hale, c.1957 (Box 16E, Folder 49)
    BG No.: A172
  - LONG AS YOU GOT YOUR HEALTH Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 16E, Folder 50)
    BG No.: A248/705
  - LOOK OF LOVE, THE Brennan, Ted (Box 16E, Folder 51)
    BG No.: G115
    Parts: cl1-2/bcl/fl1-2/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Includes 2 optional clarinet parts. Complete.
  - LOOKING FOR YESTERDAY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 16E, Folder 52)
    BG No.: A396
  - LOST, 1935 (Box 16E, Folder 53)
    BG No.: C8/175
  - LOST FOR WORDS (Box 16E, Folder 54)
    BG No.: B65
  - LOST IN MEDITATION Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 16E, Folder 55)
    Parts: saxAATT/tPt3/tbn1-2/PGB
  - LOST MY RHYTHM Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 16E, Folder 56)
    BG No.: A37/571/2
  - LOUISE Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 16E, Folder 57)
    BG No.: C375/236
    Parts: cl/tpt1-3/tbn2-3/GBD
  - LOUISIANA HAYRIDE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 01)
    Score: photocopy (see BG no. A51/98/43 for original)
  - LOUISIANA HAYRIDE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A51 / 98 / 43
    Original parts. Complete.
  - LOVE FOR SALE, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 03)
    BG No.: C30/50A
  - LOVE MAKES THE WORLD GO 'ROUND Mundy, Jimmy, c.1936 (Box 17, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A246/31
  - LOVE MAKES THE WORLD GO 'ROUND Jones, Hoyt (Box 17, Folder 05)
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD/voca1
  - LOVE ME AS I AM Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B166
  - LOVE ME BABY (Box 17, Folder 07)
    BG No.: D42/217
  - LOVE ME OR LEAVE ME Kincaide, Deane, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C358
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt1-2/tbn/PGBD
  - LOVE ME OR LEAVE ME (Box 17, Folder 09)
  - LOVE ME OR LEAVE ME Bresano, Modesto, 5/1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    BG No.: F39/7
    Parts: cl/tpt/PGBDV/fl
    Includes photocopy of published sheet music.
  - LOVE SENDS A LITTLE GIFT OF ROSES Newsom, Tommy, 3/1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    BG No.: F30/19
    Parts: cl/saxTT/tpt/PBDV
  - LOVE'S A NECESSARY THING Norman, Fred, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A215/147
  - LOVELY HULA HANDS Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 17A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D330/55
    Score: incomplete (missing page 1)
  - LOVER MAN Powell, Mel, 1946 (Box 17A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: C260/43
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/GBD/ob/horn
  - LUCKY DAY Evans, Gil, 1/30/1956 (Box 17A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B62
    Parts not indicated in SCORE
  - LULLABY IN RHYTHM Powell, Mel, 1948 (Box 17A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: 124
    Parts: cl/saxT/PBDV
  - LULLABY IN RHYTHM (Box 17A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: C10/64
  - LULLABY IN RHYTHM (HONEY CHILD) Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 17A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: B63
    Score: incomplete
  - LULU'S BACK IN TOWN Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 17A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C254/21
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1,3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    All parts are in Henderson's own hand.
  - LULU'S BACK IN TOWN Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 17A, Folder 19A)
    BG No.: 12/29/C254
    Piano part is missing last page. Chords are sketched on separate sheet for missing measures. Recopy.
  - MA BELLE MARGUERITE O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 17A, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A244
  - MABEL MABEL Cohn, Al, 1946 (Box 17A, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A210
    Written for George Auld's big band.
  - MAKE WITH THE KISSES Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 17A, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A47/141
  - MAKIN' WHOOPEE Jenkins, Gordon, 1976 (Box 17B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: G146
  - MAKIN' WHOOPEE Aless, Tony, 1959 (Box 17B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B221
  - MAMA DON'T ALLOW NO PEAS AND RICE AND COCONUT OIL Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 17B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A211/139
  - MAMA'S GONE (Box 17B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A243/833
  - MAMA'S GONE GOODBYE Hood, Bill, 6/1961 (Box 17B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: C256/250
  - MAMA, THAT MOON IS HERE AGAIN Henderson, Fletcher, 1937 (Box 17B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: C121/247
    Included are parts in B flat for: saxT/GB (slightly different), and autographed Robin-Rainger "work copy" sheet music. Complete.
  - MAN AND HIS DREAMS, A Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 17B, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A249
  - MAN I LOVE, THE Knepper, Jimmy, 5/1962 (Box 17B, Folder 30)
    BG No.: D443/286
  - MANDY IS TWO Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 17B, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A212
  - MANHATTAN SERENADE Thompson, Johnny, 1942 (Box 17B, Folder 32)
    BG No.: D19/50A
    Parts: cl/saxAAB/tpt1/tbn1/PBD
  - MARCHIN' AND SWINGIN' Karlin, Fred, 10/1959 (Box 17C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: D81/3
  - MARIA Karlin, Fred, 11/10/1959 (Box 17C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: D221/16
    Parts: cl/PGBDV/f1
  - MARIE Henderson, Fletcher (Box 17C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A50/3850/47
  - MARY HAD A LITTLE LAMB Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 17C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A236
  - MARY HAD A LITTLE SLAM Powell, Mel, 1945 (Box 17C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A208/107
  - MAY I NEVER LOVE AGAIN Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 17C, Folder 38)
    BG No.: A242/27E
  - ME AND YOU (Box 17C, Folder 39)
    BG No.: F26
    Parts: cl/P
  - MEADOWLAND Lipman, Joe, 4/15/1962 (Box 17D, Folder 40)
    BG No.: F7/262
  - MEAN TO ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 17D, Folder 40A)
    BG No.: 127/C52/7
  - MEDLEY Stegmeyer, Bill, 1960 (Box 17D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: D354/64
    Medley of: "Don't Be That Way", "Stompin' at the Savoy", "Sunny Side of the Street", et al. Seven tunes in all. Complete.
  - MEDLEY Lipman, Joe, 1961 (Box 17D, Folder 42)
    BG No.: G33/259
    Medley of: "Don't Be That Way", "Stompin' at the Savoy", "Sunny Side of the Street", "Rose Room", "Moonglow", "...Angels Sing".
  - MEDLEY Kincaide, Deane, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 01)
    BG No.: C161/221
    Medley of: "I've Gotta Right To Sing the Blues", "I Hadn't Any one 'Til You", and "I've Got You Under My Skin".
  - MEET THE BAND Prince, Bob, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 02)
    BG No.: G26/308
  - MELODY FARM Martin, Skip, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A238/6
  - MEMORIES OF YOU Pleis, Jack, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 04)
    BG No.: B227
    Key: 9 flat
  - MEMORY OF A ROSE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A393
  - MEMPHIS BLUES Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 06)
    BG No.: C271/77/309E/B168
  - MEMPHIS BLUES Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 07)
    Score: photocopy (for original see BG no.271/77/B168)
  - MENDELSSOHN MOWED DOWN Templeton, Alec, 1939 (Box 18A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C335/17/408B
    Score: condensed and not of full arrangement.
    Parts: cl1-4/bcl/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PBD
    No sax parts.
  - MERRY-GO-ROUND BROKE DOWN, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B254
  - MESSAGE FROM THE MAN IN THE MOON Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A394
  - MEXICO JOE, 1943 (Box 18A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A395
  - MIDGETS, THE Newman, Joe, c.1962 (Box 18A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: F25
    Drum part copied on the back of the piano part.
  - MIDNIGHT EXPRESS Roumanis, George, 1957 (Box 18A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D43/214
  - MIDNIGHT IN MOSCOW Nelson, Oliver, 4/1962 (Box 18A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D423/ 281
  - MIDNIGHT IN MOSCOW Lipman, Joe, 4/22/1962 (Box 18B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D423/273
  - MILENBERG JOYS Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 18B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: B66/M1/105
  - MINNE THE MOOCHER'S WEDDING DAY Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 18B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: A323/117
  - MINNIE'S IN THE MONEY Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 18B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: C334/A403
    From the film "The Gang's All Here".
  - MINNIE'S IN THE MONEY (Box 18B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C334/32B
  - MISSION TO MOSCOW (Box 18C, Folder 20)
    BG No.: C210/8988
    Parts: cl/saxAATB(-T2)/tpt1-3(2)4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    These parts are photocopies and a transcription from record for Glenn Gray; this is NOT the original arrangement.
  - MISSION TO MOSCOW, 1959 (Box 18C, Folder 21)
    BG No.: G128
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/tbn/rhythm lead sheet(3)DV
  - MISSION TO MOSCOW Powell, Mel, 1942 (Box 18C, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C210/M2
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGB
    These parts are photocopies except for one clarinet and tpt4.
  - MIST IS OVER THE MOON, A Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 18C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: A217
  - MISTER AND MISSUS FITCH Wilbur, Bob, 1976 (Box 18C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: G39
  - MISTER AND MISSUS FITCH Feller, Sid, 1958 (Box 18C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: B373/249
  - MISTER DEEP BLUE SEA Henderson, Fletcher, c.1935 (Box 18C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A16/305/23
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PBD/banjo
  - MISTER FIVE BY FIVE Sauter, Eddie, 1942 (Box 18C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A151
  - MISTER MEADOWLARK Brooks, Dudley, 1940 (Box 18D, Folder 28)
    BG No.: 313
  - MOMENT OF TRUTH South, Harry (Box 18D, Folder 29)
    BG No.: G113/T6
    Vocal arrangement for Barbara Jay.
  - MONDAY IN MANHATTAN Murphy, Spud, 11/10/1935 (Box 18D, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A152/23
  - MOOD I'M IN, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B255
  - MOOD INDIGO Clayton, Buck, 1959 (Box 18D, Folder 32)
  - MOON ABOUT TOWN Sauter, Eddie (Box 18D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: A324
  - MOON FROM THE EAST Dameron, Tadd, 5/1962 (Box 18D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: D445/307
    Sax doubles: A1-cl, A2-fl, T2-fl. Complete.
  - MOON GOT IN MY EYES, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: B256
    Parts: G
  - MOON IS A SILVER DOLLAR, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 18D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A291
  - MOON OF MANAKOORA Stegmeyer, Bill, 9/1960 (Box 18D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: D331/56
  - MOONLIGHT AND SHADOWS Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: A64/207
  - MOONLIGHT ON THE GANGES Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 18D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: C261/18
    Parts: saxAATB(-T1)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - MOONLIGHT ON THE HIGHWAY Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: B115/41
  - MOONLIGHT SERENADE (Box 18E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: A56/M4
    Parts: saxAAATT/bcl/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PG(2)BD
    Arrangement played by Glenn Miller Band.
  - MOONLIGHT SERENADE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 18E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: A56/547
  - MORE THAN EVER Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 18E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: B114
  - MORE THAN YOU KNOW (Box 18A, Folder 43A)
    BG No.: 26/93/56
    All but one clarinet part are photocopies.
  - MORITAT (Box 18E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: B68/167
  - MOUNTAIN GREENERY Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 06)
  - MUDDY WATER Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: A148
  - MUSKRAT RAMBLE Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 18E, Folder 45A)
    BG No.: B64/18/23
  - MUTINY IN THE PARLOR Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 18F, Folder 46)
    BG No.: A149/12
  - MY BEST WISHES Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 18F, Folder 47)
    BG No.: A150/725
  - MY FAVORITE THINGS Karlin, Fred, 10/1959 (Box 18F, Folder 48)
    BG No.: D222
  - MY FIRST THRILL Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 18F, Folder 49)
    BG No.: D32/208
  - MY GAL SAL Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 18F, Folder 50)
    BG No.: C357/134
  - MY GREATEST MISTAKE (Box 18F, Folder 51)
    BG No.: 178E/332
  - MY HEAD SAYS YES BUT MY HEART SAYS NO Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 18F, Folder 52)
    BG No.: A235
  - MY HEART BELONGS TO DADDY Albam, Manny, 1962 (Box 18F, Folder 53)
    BG No.: D431/284
  - MY HONEY Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 18F, Folder 54)
    BG No.: A251/17
  - MY HONEY'S LOVING ARMS Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 18F, Folder 55)
    BG No.: A189/157/25
  - MY HONEY'S LOVING ARMS Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 18F, Folder 55A)
    BG No.: 25
    Recopy. Rhythm parts used with this set in the 1980's are part of original set, BG no.A189/157.
  - MY IDEAL Thompson, Johnny, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 01)
    BG No.: C356/18
  - MY LAST GOODBYE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B118
  - MY LITTLE COUSIN (Box 19, Folder 03)
    BG No.: 49A
    Parts: cl/saxA(-A2)
  - MY LITTLE COUSIN Powell, Mel, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 04)
    BG No.: D17/49A
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt1/PGB
  - MY LITTLE GRASS SHACK Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 05)
    BG No.: D334/59
  - MY LOVER Williams, George, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B374/247
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - MY LOVER Williams, George, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 07)
    BG No.: B374
    Parts: cl/(fl/cl)/ob/tpt/tbn/PGBD/voca1
  - MY MY Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 08)
    BG No.: A42/297
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt103/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - MY OHIO HOME (Box 19, Folder 09)
    BG No.: C355
  - MY OLD FLAME Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B169/14
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpti-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - MY OLD FLAME Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B169
    Score: intro to rehearsal letter B only
    Tbn3 and drum parts are taped to the back of the corresponding parts in the other arrangement (BG no.B169/14). Music to letter B only.
  - MY ONE AND ONLY LOVE (Box 19A, Folder 12)
    Parts: cl(3)/rhythm lead sheet(3)
  - MY PRAYER Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 19A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: B119
  - MY REVERIE Lipman, Joe, 9/1961 (Box 19A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D408/252
  - MY SHINING HOUR Clayton, Buck, c.1945 (Box 19A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B69
  - NAUGHTY WALTZ Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 19A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: C233/213
  - NEARNESS OF YOU, THE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 19A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B208/328/709B
    Included also are pencil parts for saxB and tbn2 on same sheet. Tbn2 differs slightly from manuscript part and tbn3 in score.
  - NEARNESS OF YOU, THE Cohn, Al; Van Lake, Turk (Box 19A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: B208
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/PG("solo" and "rhythm")BD
  - NEVER FALL IN LOVE AGAIN Ogerman, Claus, c.1960 (Box 19A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: G35/N1
  - NEW DEAL IN LOVE Jenkins, Gordon, 1935 (Box 19B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B92/19/99
  - NEW DELHI (Box 19B, Folder 21)
    Parts: cl/PB,
  - NEW KIND OF LOVE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 19B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B209/8
    Clarinet, tbn2-3, piano and guitar are from another copy and added to this set to complete it. Complete.
  - NEW KIND OF LOVE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 19B, Folder 23)
    Score: photocopy (for original see BG no.209/8)
    These parts are a later recopy. Complete.
  - NEW KIND OF LOVE Henderson, Fletcher (Box 19B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B209/C236/N2/3/8
    SaxB/tpt4/tbn3 from a later copy. Complete.
  - NEW KIND OF LOVE Henderson, Fletcher (Box 19B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: C236
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn2/P
    These parts do not correspond to Henderson D flat score. Parts are in Henderson's own hand.
  - NEW TOWN BLUE TOWN Evans, Gil, c.1955 (Box 19B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: B307/164
  - NICKEL TO MY NAME Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B93
  - NIGHT Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B170
    Key: E flat minor
  - NIGHT AND DAY (Box 19C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: C9/172
  - NIGHT AND DAY Henderson, Fletcher (Box 19C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: C9/103
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2
    Original parts in Henderson's hand. These parts match other arrangement by Henderson, except for key.
  - NIGHT AND DAY Henderson, Fletcher (Box 19C, Folder 31)
    Parts: cl/PGBD
    These parts mesh with other Henderson arrangement except for key.
  - NO MATTER WHAT MAY HAPPEN Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 19C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A388/13/107
    Parts: tbn1
  - NO OTHER ONE Murphy, Spud, 11/1935 (Box 19C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: A389/29
  - NO WAY TO STOP IT Karlin, Fred, 10/1959 (Box 19C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: D214/14
  - NOBODY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: B261
  - NOBODY KNOWS THE TROUBLE I'VE SEEN Karlin, Fred, 5/7/1960 (Box 19C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: D303/35
  - NOBODY'S HEART Feller, Sid, 1958 (Box 19C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B376
    Parts: cl/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/vocal
  - NOBODY'S HEART Previn, Andre, 1958 (Box 19D, Folder 38)
    Arranged for Betty Bennett.
  - NOT MINE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: B173/10A
  - NOTES TO YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 19D, Folder 40)
    BG No.: 106
    Also known as "Henderson's Stomp". These parts are from a later recopy.